RG 062:032, Town of Coventry
Connecticut State Library
Town of Coventry records
1783-1926
Connecticut State Library
Coventry (Conn.)
24 cubic feet
Administrative and tax records for the town of Coventry.
RG062_032
T000989
Historical Note
The town of Coventry was incorporated in May 1712.
Scope and Content
Administrative and tax records for the town of Coventry.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Coventry -- Regsiters; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Coventry -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Coventry -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Coventry -- Registers; Voting registers -- Connecticut -- Coventry; Elections -- Connecticut -- Coventry -- Statistics; Voting -- Connecticut -- Coventry -- Statistics; Public welfare -- Connecticut -- Coventry
Places:
Coventry (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1783-1926
  - Registers of electors, 1840-1926 (Box Boxes 1-2)
  - Town records, including attachments, legal records, town meeting notices, records of votes, records relating to care of the poor, bills, receipts, orders, dog licenses, vital records, estimates for building bridges, pledges for town chairman, 1808-1921 (Box Box 3)
  - Tax Records (Box Box 4)
    - Andover Society rate bill, 1784 (1783?) (Box Box 4)
    - Andover Society highway Tax rate bills, 1794, 1808, 1840, 1844, 1845 (Box Box 4)
    - Andover Society rate list, 1805 (Box Box 4)
    - North Coventry rate lists, 1837, 1838 (Box Box 4)
    - Tax collector's and assessor's notices and correspondence, 1881-1913 (Box Box 4)
    - Abatment lists, 1900-1905 (Box Box 4)
    - Collector's Returns, 1908-1917 (Box Box 4)
  - Individual Tax Lists
    - 1884 and 1904-1907 (Box Box 5)
    - 1907-1908 (Box Box 6)
    - 1912, 1 volume
    - 1913, 1 volume
    - 1914, 1 volume
    - 1915, 1 volume
    - 1916, 1 volume
    - 1917, 1 volume
    - 1918, 1 volume
    - 1919, 1 volume
    - 1920, 1 volume
  - Tax Abstracts
    For each year there is a seperate tax abstract for the first society and second society. For 1855 there is only a second society tax abstract.
    Box 23 is on oversize shelving.
    - 1855, 1856, 1857, 1858, 1859 (Box Box 7)
    - 1860, 1861, 1862, 1863, 1864 (Box Box 8)
    - 1865, 1866, 1867, 1868, 1869 (Box Box 9)
    - 1870, 1871, 1872, 1873, 1874 (Box Box 10)
    - 1875, 1876, 1877, 1878, 1879 (Box Box 11)
    - 1880, 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884 (Box Box 12)
    - 1885, 1886, 1887 (Box Box 13)
    - 1888, 1889 (Box Box 14)
    - 1890, 1891, 1892 (Box Box 15)
    - 1893, 1894, 1895, 1896 (Box Box 16)
    - 1897, 1898, 1899 (Box Box 17)
    - 1900, 1901, 1902 (Box Box 18)
    - 1903, 1904, 1905 (Box Box 19)
    - 1906, 1907, 1908 (Box Box 20)
    - 1909, 1910, 1911 (Box Box 21)
    - 1912, 1913 (Box Box 22)
    - 1914, 1915, 1916 (Box Box 23)